{
	"questions":[
		{
			"question":"What does the expression below return?\r\nlet fruit = {name: 'apple'};\r\nlet fruititem = {name: 'apple'};\r\nconsole.log(fruit === fruititem);",
			"answers":[
				"false",
				"true",
				"undefined",
				"Reference Error"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 0
		},
		{
			"question":"What does the expression below return?\r\nlet fruit = {name: 'apple'};\r\nlet fruititem = fruit;\r\nconsole.log(fruit === fruititem);",
			"answers":[
				"false",
				"true",
				"undefined",
				"Reference Error"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 1
		},
		{
			"question":"How to compare two objects?",
			"answers":[
				"obj1 == obj2",
				"obj1 === obj2",
				"Create two object property arrays with getOwnPropertynames(obj#) and compare their corresponding elements",
				"JSON.stringify(obj1) === JSON.stringify(obj2)"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 3
		},
		{
			"question":"How to check if object is empty?",
			"answers":[
				"if(obj.length == 0)",
				"if(obj.length === 0)",
				"JSON.stringify(myObj) === '{}'",
				"JSON.stringify(myObj) === {}"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 2
		},
		{
			"question":"Which expression is incorrect?",
			"answers":[
				"obj.prop1",
				"obj['prop name']",
				"obj.1prop",
				"obj['1prop']"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 2
		},
		{
			"question":"How it is not recommended to clone an array in Javascript?",
			"answers":[
				"let array2 = array1.slice()",
				"let array2 = array1.concat()",
				"let array2 = array1",
				"let array2 = Array.from(array1)"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 2
		},
		{
			"question":"What is the result of the expression below?\r\nlet array = new Array(2);\r\nconsole.log(array);",
			"answers":[
				"[2, 2]",
				"[undefined, undefined]",
				"[null, null]",
				"[0, 0]"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 1
		},
		{
			"question":"What is the result of the expression below?\r\nlet array = new Array(2);\r\nconsole.log(array.length);",
			"answers":[
				"0",
				"undefined",
				"Reference Error",
				"2"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 3
		},
		{
			"question":"What is the result of the expression below?\r\nNumber('1') - 1 == 0;",
			"answers":[
				"true",
				"false",
				"null",
				"undefined"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 0
		},
		{
			"question":"What is the result of the expression below?\r\nnew Array(5).toString();",
			"answers":[
				"[]",
				"'[]'",
				"',,,,'",
				"'[null,null,null,null,null]'"
			],
			"correctAnswerIndex": 2
		}
	]
}